pumpitupparty.com 2009-06-28

# Privacy Policy | Pum It Up

We want you to enjoy every visit to www.pumpitupparty.com, whether you're here to participate in our Birthday Club, reserve a party or to tell us about your last trip to one of our locations. So rest assured, any information you share with us, from your email address to your favorite memory at Pump It Up, will be carefully guarded through our use of industry-standard security software. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy. Pump It Up reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time. Be sure to check this page periodically for updates. This policy applies only to personal information collected online at www.pumpitupparty.com and does not apply to information collected offline by Pump It Up. This policy is effective May 31, 2006. 

## What kind of information we ask for and why.

### Promotional Events.

If you choose to take part in a promotional event, we'll ask for any information necessary to the administration of the event such as your name, email address, and shipping address. We may, on occasion, co-sponsor promotions with third parties. We will notify you at the time of collection if third parties will obtain your personal information. 

### Surveys.

From time-to-time we may post surveys on our Site. The surveys may request demographic information (such as age range, gender, areas of interest, and familiarity with Pump It Up products and services) and customer feedback. Participation in these requests is completely voluntary and with each request you will have the choice of whether or not to disclose information. Such survey information will be used to improve the overall experience on www.pumpitupparty.com .  

### Aggregate Information.

We collect Aggregate Information about you and your use of our Website whenever you visit us online. For instance, we may collect various forms of "click stream" information such as entry and exit points for our Web site (i.e., referring URLs or domains), site traffic statistics, page views, impressions, and operating system and browser type. In addition, when users request pages on our Web site, our servers automatically log their IP addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web. This Aggregate Information generally will not personally identify you or be correlated to you individually for external purposes. We may collect, compile, store, publish, promote, report, sell, or otherwise disclose or use any and all Aggregate Information, provided that, such information does not personally identify you. When we share such information with other companies, it is not traceable to any particular user, and will not be used to contact you. If we do correlate any Aggregate Information to you, such information will be treated like any other Personal Information under this policy. 

### E-Mail Updates

Unless we hear from you otherwise, we'll email you occasional updates about new additions to this site, special offers you can take advantage of at your local Pump It Up, and updates about our sister brand Pump It Up Jr. If at any time you decide you'd rather not receive this type of information from us, simply click on the opt out link in the email and select the option to be removed from email updates/promotions or the option to be removed from the Birthday Club entirely.  

### Disclosures

Your personal information registered in Pump It Up Birthday Club will be shared with our sister brand, Pump It Up Jr., and our affiliates who may need, for example, to reserve your parties, respond to your requests or inquiries, or help us improve our products or website. We require our affiliates to respect our privacy practices and not use your personal information for purposes other than to carry out our instructions. Pump It Up reserves the right to use or disclose any information as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request, to protect the integrity of the site, to fulfill your requests, or to cooperate in any law enforcement investigation or an investigation on a matter of public safety. 

### Disclosures

Your personal information registered in Pump It Up Birthday Club will be shared with our sister brand, Pump It Up Jr., and our affiliates who may need, for example, to reserve your parties, respond to your requests or inquiries, or help us improve our products or website. We require our affiliates to respect our privacy practices and not use your personal information for purposes other than to carry out our instructions. Pump It Up reserves the right to use or disclose any information as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request, to protect the integrity of the site, to fulfill your requests, or to cooperate in any law enforcement investigation or an investigation on a matter of public safety. 

### Company Sale

Information collected through our Web site is considered a trade secret of Pump It Up. As the owner of such information, we may disclose or sell such information as an asset of the company in conjunction with the sale to a third party of our company or a portion of our assets. 

### Franchising Information

For franchise information on Pump It Up please visit our Web site. The Franchise Opportunity Web Site collects personal information from candidates. 

### Children's Information

Pump It Up recognizes the need to provide additional privacy protection to children. Children 12 years old and younger may visit www.pumpitupparty.com without disclosing any personally identifiable information. However, it is sometimes necessary to collect some personally identifiable information about children in order to allow them to use a feature of our site (like joining the Pump It Up Birthday Club). In addition, be aware that all sites that are targeted to children 12 and younger are prohibited by law from collecting more information than they need. Only a parent or guardian may register a child 12 or younger for the Pump It Up Birthday Club. When a parent registers a child for the Birthday Club, we request the child's name, date of birth and parent's e-mail address. We collect this information in order to verify the child's age, send personalized Birthday Club e-cards, and provide other Birthday Club benefits (such as sweepstakes, newsletters, e-cards and special offers. We require our affiliates and franchisees to respect our privacy practices concerning children's information and not use children's information for purposes other than to carry out our instructions. Parents may request at any time that we delete information about their children from our databases. To do so, as a parent, when an email message is sent to you, select the option to be removed from the Birthday Club entirely.  

### Links

You may find that it is possible to "hot-link" from other web sites to this, the official Pump It Up web site, or from this web site to other web sites. Those other web sites are not under our control. Pump It Up is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other web sites. You should consult the privacy policy of the site to or from which you link to determine the information practices of that site. 

### Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding our privacy practices, you can telephone or write to us at Pump It Up. Our contact information is: 

PIU Management, LLC  
1860 W. University Dr., Suite 108  
Tempe, AZ 85281  
Phone: 480-371-1200
